棒极了  现在我们知道我们可以通过
Cool. Now that we know that we can use
日志工具调试我们的程序  我们将返回到
logging to debug our app, we're going to return to
网络请求的那个代码片段  把它放到我们的程序里
this networking code snippet here and drop it into
通过网络请求获取真实的天气数据
the sunshine app to query for actual weather data. Open
打开项目工程的的MainActivity.java这个文件
up your project in MainActivity.java. In this class,
往下拉  找到PlaceholderFragment这个类
scroll down to the PlaceholderFragment class. Within the
在它的OnCreateView()这个方法中  再往下拉
PlaceholderFragment class in the OnCreateView method, scroll down
把网络请求部分的代码粘贴到这里
and go ahead and add the networking code snippet here.
或者保持留白  等你什么时候想粘过来了再粘  你或许需要启用
To get her blank, is pasted below again if you need it. You may need to enable
Auto Import 中的这些选项或者手动添加import
these options in auto import or add the imports
你可以看看下面的介绍  当你运行你的应用程序时
manually. See the instructions below. When you run the
你会发现它崩溃了
app, you'll see that is crashes. Use log
使用LogCat工具检查一下
cat to figure out which error is the guilty
导致应用崩溃的原因吧  我们把它留作测验题
culprit that caused the crash. We're assuming that for
你需要用3.0以上版本的 Android 设备
this quiz question. You're using a device that's running
虚拟机也成
honeycomb or later. Use the emulator if needed.